I'm so hungry, Shido!
Shido, gotta potty.
Darling! Darling!
Oh, Shido, what's going on?
Kaguya, isn't that my candy you're about to eat?
Come on, don't sweat it.
If stupid little things like that actually get to you,
then you might as well be as old as you look right now.
Agree. It's much nicer to share, and you have plenty.
Hey!
Everybody listen!
I need all of you to calm down right this second!
Masumi, what have you done to me?
You've got a lot on your hands today, Shin.
Reina! Thank goodness.
I appreciate you coming.
It's hard to keep up with all of them on my own.
Sure. I'm sorry for having to leave them here.
Houseguests are a lot of work.
Um, so what happened to Natsumi?
I deployed observation devices to find her, but no luck yet.
I'll let you know if that changes.
All right, thanks.
It's strange. Why would Natsumi do something like this?
I've asked myself that.
It could have been some sort of last resort.
Emergency measures she used to escape.
The spirits no longer have the ability to fight.
It could be.
This is actually a warning not to go looking for her.
Of course, she could also just have a grudge.
As far as we've confirmed, there are six spirits gathered around Shido Itsuka.
So as soon as you're feeling ready, I'll have you make your move, Ellen.
Right. Who shall I start with, sir?
Uh, yes. This is the spirit from the AST's report the other day.
She hasn't been confirmed lost as of yet.
And seeing as she turned up in Tengu City, she's our primary target.
A grand opening amidst the chaos.
My own personal zoo.
Now, Shido's fathering skills are put to the test.
A grand opening amidst the chaos.
Spacealles 상황.
Spacehehehe.
Space.
Science.
See you next time.
No way!
Seriously?
That's so lame!
Well, at least it looks like Natsumi spared everyone here.
Morning, Itsuka.
Hey.
You okay?
Oh, yeah. I'm super good.
Excuse me, Itsuka?
Yes?
You have some guests here to see you, but I'm not sure if...
What guests?
Yeah, about that.
See? I knew he was here!
Hey, what did I say?
If you were to stay in the office and behave until I came back!
Well, well, what have we here?
Mother, you're blocking the way.
Shito, do you copy?
It's an emergency!
Toka and the others have disappeared from the house!
Yeah, that's because they came here.
Hey, Shito, would you please do us all a favor and have a talk with his teachers and set them straight?
They refuse to believe we're really Amai!
Sai, these adults don't have enough imagination not to judge on appearances.
Why are you here in the first place when I asked you all to wait at home?
It's a school day, so we didn't think you actually meant it.
Yes, I know it's a school day.
Hey, Kyuri!
Wanna tell us your name?
I'm Chiyogami Itsuka, and I'm so happy to meet some of Papa's friends.
Hold up, Papa?
No, no, don't misunderstand.
These, uh, these girls are, uh, my relative's kids.
I'm just looking after them.
You know, Papa, it's only like, uh, it's their nickname for me.
Ah, now I get it.
It's funny, but knowing you, I almost believe the kids could be yours.
Well, that's terrifying.
Come on, everyone, let's get you back home now.
Oh, weird.
What was that?
Choka, what?
What have you done to me, Shito?
Bastard!
What the hell did you just do?
You're the worst!
That is so lame!
But I didn't do anything!
Wait, the light!
Don't tell me.
Come on, time to go!
Ugh, you coward!
Shito!
What, Kotiri?
The house!
The house?
Hold on, what about the house?
Of course, why not?
She's really done it this time.
Now, I wonder what I can do to mess with these fools next.
You seriously don't intend to react after what Westcott did to us?
I'm not sure what to tell you.
The incident did make one thing clear.
Westcott's on a whole different level.
We were foolish to think we could stand against him.
Maybe so.
But he still deserves every single ounce of retribution we can serve him.
Retribution, huh?
What exactly is it you have in mind?
Right now, as far as we know, Westcott is in Japan, correct?
Yeah, and what of it?
I'm home, girls.
Why is there so much cake?
Girls
These past few days have been one thing after another again
What's with this outfit come on do you copy Reina help Natsumi has gone all out this time
Although thanks to that. I've been able to track down her location. Wow for real. Well, where is she?
Man this is so great. You look ridiculous
Ridiculous, and it only serves you right for embarrassing me. What will I do next?
Shoot who's coming this way some friend of Shido's maybe too bad. I guarantee you won't be catching me this time
You know I never would have expected such a violent greeting from one of Shido's friends
Sorry to disappoint, but I wouldn't exactly call myself a friend of his. Oh
You must be with the AST then not that I could possibly care any less. What do you want?
It's simple I've come here to hunt you down
You might find that difficult
Well, we'll only know for sure once I try right
Where do you get all this confidence from them?
No, well, no difference to me
You witch
Anya!
My, my, my. Thank you so very much for this abundance of goodies. Now to return the favor
Look what she did. Is that Ellen?
I must say I think you're cuter this way
So exactly what do you plan to do this fight isn't over yet Natsumi? I'm still powerful enough to kill you
No, no, why?
How could this be happening?
No, no, please no
I must have missed your vitals
But I'm afraid your power is falling rapidly
Now then
Please, someone help me, anybody, please I'm begging
Don't you worry, it's gonna be over soon
Hmm
Yeah! No, no, leaving 419人
Are you alright?
Yeah? But why are you...
Now Gabriel, let's round up
That's wonderful
Pathetic! Look how weak you are.
Sympathy. It is a shame.
Why are they helping?
Natsumi!
Wait, what are you doing?
Are you okay? We'll patch you up in no time.
And why would I let that happen?
Hey, Ellen, think twice on this.
Your friends are in short supply.
And you're outnumbered.
Doesn't bother me.
Truth be told, those girls were never much help from the start.
Is that right? Well then...
Miku!
Kodori, do it now!
Hang in there a little bit longer, Natsumi.
Shida, why help me?
A useful pawn could come in handy.
Mr. Simpson.
Tell us, at this very moment, do you know how many DEM satellites are in geosynchronous orbit?
No.
The answer is 23.
And out of those, I'm told eight are awaiting disposal.
Hold on, back up a minute.
Where are you going with this?
I mean, what does it have to do with a...
Huh?
Murdoch, no!
You can't mean...
Yes, I do.
We should dispose of them.
We can gather up all those junk satellites and drop them on Tengu City.
Yes?
Punishment?
You mean mine?
What are you saying?
There you are.
No, not at亲 size.
Oh no, butён that Prince.
Yeah.
All this is to punish me?
What the hell is going on?
That sure was quick, Shido.
Is it true? Natsumi woke up?
Just a little bit ago.
Natsumi.
She took enough damage from Ellen that we don't have to worry about her using her angel.
But still, you should be careful.
Right.
Hey, what happened to your face?
Well, like I said, be on your guard.
Oh, wow. Okay.
Yo, Natsumi.
What the? Would you cut that out, please?
Don't look at me!
Come on, what's the matter?
Why did you rescue me? I don't get it.
Why?
Well, because Ellen obviously had you beat.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Look, I mean, I went around impersonating you, and then I erased all of your friends!
I don't know what to tell you.
When we came across you in that condition, of course we were gonna help.
Stop lying to me!
Don't you think you can fool me with your smooth talk, Shido?
That's not even close to my intention.
Natsumi, listen.
What is it?
Tell me this. Why'd you do this stuff? Why did you erase my friends?
Why do you think? Because you saw the real me and know my secret, obviously!
And that secret is...
Well, that this is...
This is my true form.
Hold on just a sec.
Why does me seeing you in this form set you off so badly?
How can you ask that?
Please!
How can I not be mortified looking like this?
No one should ever see me this way!
Not Sumi.
Listen, I...
The first time you and I met, you said I was pretty. Do you even remember that?
Would you have had the same reaction if I had looked like this?
The answer is no! You would have ignored me if I'd spoken to you!
I really don't think...
Yes, you would have!
Everyone's exactly the same!
When I look like this, nobody ever pays attention to me, and it's the worst thing ever!
In any case, that's why I'll never be able to forgive anyone who has seen me in my true form!
And that includes you, so get lost!
Can I ask you something?
What is it that's so disappointing about the current you?
Yeah, that's kind of why I told you to be careful.
That was not Sumi's mental state.
Well, it's been incredibly unstable.
Sealing her is out of the question at this point.
Figured as much.
She's miserable.
She just doesn't have any confidence in her current state.
Obviously.
Otherwise, she wouldn't always be changing herself.
You know, I actually think the real Natsumi has a charm of her own.
I just wish there was a way for her to see it.
She'd rather transform than to look in the mirror long enough to see that.
Transform?
Can I ask you something?
What is it that's so disappointing about the current you?
Come on.
Who would be fooled by that?
Once I can finally use Hanyal again, I am so done with this.
What's this?
Chapter!
Let me go!
Okay, we're good.
Hey, where am I?
Hi there.
This is a pop-up beauty salon.
You're in Salon de Miku.
Huh?
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Miku just explained.
It's a day of beauty.
No, nothing's ever that simple.
I bet you're really doing this to make me believe you think I'm pretty while you laugh at me behind my back.
Whatever.
Would you lie down already?
You're really holding up the schedule.
Schedule?
Natsumi, for the rest of the day, our goal is to transform you in a way that makes you happy.
If we succeed, then that's our win.
If you don't see a difference, then we lose.
And you can do as you please.
What exactly do you mean, do as I please?
Let's see.
What if we let you run away to wherever you might want to go?
Fine, deal.
It's about time for you to learn a girl can transform even without an angel if she wants to.
We're going to start by oiling up your skin.
How could this help?
Now we're just going to warm you with some hot stones.
How does that feel?
I mean, it's all right.
This will help any swelling in your legs, too.
Oh, really?
Doesn't that feel nice?
You really have to be taking better care of your gorgeous skin.
Why should it matter what I do when...
I mean, it won't change.
Somebody had a little nap.
Move along to the next room now.
You can sit back and trust our mad skills.
Clothes are important for your confidence.
Come, follow up.
Step right on in.
Oh, that looks awesome.
Yeah, it's really cute.
Try on this one next.
That brings us here to the final room of your transformative journey.
Hi, my name's Shiori.
Makeup's my thing, and you're getting a makeover.
I just...
I don't think it'll change anything.
Do you honestly believe that?
Of course I do.
What if I told you...
Underneath here, I'm really a man.
Weirdo.
Poor thing.
Look how hurt he is.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Besides, if you ignore the silly part about Darling being a guy, he's still a girl.
Yeah, anyways...
I'll be utilizing these skills, the same technique you couldn't see through just now,
to prove that I can transform you.
Do whatever you want.
I'm all finished.
How is it, Natsumi?
I don't know.
Is this me?
Wait.
What the heck is going on here?
And why does everyone look so happy?
I did those terrible things.
If this is me, that means I just lost because...
I might...
I think I'm...
Hey, Natsumi, watch out!
Uh...
Who is this?
My name is Ellen Mathers.
I'm trying to reach Master Sergeant Tobeichi.
Is this she?
Ellen Mathers, huh?
What is this about?
I like that.
Let's get straight to the point.
Master Sergeant, I want you to consider coming to work for me.
No way.
I'm not aiding any organization that would bring harm to Shido.
There she is!
That way!
Uh-oh.
Looks like you're in quite the predicament.
Five years ago, there was a fire in Tengu City.
If you do decide to work for me, you would be given access to information on that event.
You want to avenge your parents, don't you?
I'll do it.
What the...
You're a smart girl.
Welcome to DEM Industries.
One way.
Okay.
whiskey, please.
Please do.
Oh, okay.
No way.
Thank you.